天使们正在相互残杀
Angels are slaughtering one another.
已经正式开战了
It's an open warfare.
这里发生了什么
What happened here.
一个奇怪的天使现身了
A strange angel arrived.
他说他受命于新的上帝
He said he worked for the new God.
我会找到Metatron 然后让他血债血偿
I will find Metatron and I will make him pay.
去领导那些反叛我的天使 Castiel
Lead the angels against me,Castiel.
我知道你的真实身份
I know who you really are.
Gadreel
Gadreel.
你对我有什么企图 Metatron
What is it that you want of me,Metatron.
重建天堂
Rebuilt heaven.
如果你想做我的二把手
You want to be my second in command.
先证明你准备好了
Prove you are ready.
你找到他的时候
When you find him.
说Poughkeepsie
Say Poughkeepsie.
Poughkeepsie
Poughkeepsie.
这是我们的暗语
It's our code word.
意思是什么都别管 赶紧跑
Means drop everything and run.
控制住 Sam
Take control,Sam.
把他驱逐出去
Cast him out.
Metatron指使Gadreel杀了Kevin
Metatron made Gadreel kill Kevin.
这下事情就说通了
It explains a lot.
快啊
Now.
动手啊 杀了我
Do it.Kill me.
这正合你意 是不是
You'd like that,wouldn't you.
你就坐在这里烂掉吧
You can sit here and rot.
你是不是故意让Winchester两兄弟抓住我的
Was the Winchesters' grabbing me part of your plan.
那是预料之外的
That was a surprise.
但是我知道一件他们不知道的事
But I know something they don't know.
我知道结局
The ending.
Abaddon 她是个恶魔
Abaddon,she's a demon.
也是个地狱骑士
Who is a knight of hell.
你知道我从衣柜里穿越过来之后
You know what I find most shocking.
最让我惊讶的事情是什么吗
In my time traveling through closet.
竟然有人觉得
Somebody thought it was a good idea.
应该让你当地狱之王
To make you the King of Hell.
我是你的王
I am your king.
你和我得谈谈改朝换代的事了
You and I have to talk about regime change.
子弹上刻有恶魔陷阱
A devil's trap carved in a bullet.
防止你化成黑烟逃跑
It can keep you from smoking out.
地狱骑士不是那么容易死的
The knight of hell isn't exactly the dying kind.
但是有个东西能杀死地狱骑士
But there's something that can kill a knight.
初刃
The First Blade.
那是该死的该隐之印
It's the bloody mark of Cain.
没有这个印 初刃毫无用处
Without the mark,the blade is useless.
该隐之印可以传给值得的人
The mark can be transferred to someone who's worthy.
但你得知道 这个印记随之而来的沉重负担
But you have to know with the mark comes a great burden.
他可以差遣地狱之犬
He sends in hell hounds.
恶魔的斗牛犬
Demonic pitbulls.
你可以控制它们吗
You can control them.
去咬他
Sic him boy.
但你现在一团糟
But you are here a mess.
你的DNA
It's your DNA.
就是我的海洛因 太过上瘾
It's my addition makes you needy.
你把我的一言一行都汇报给了Abaddon
You reported everything I did back to Abaddon
(利斯 苏格兰)
你说什么
What's that you said.
请进吗
Come in.
不介意我进来了吧
Don't mind if I do.
你是谁
Who are you.
你想干什么
What do you want.
我是你亲戚的一个朋友
A friend of the family.
我想要你
And I want you.
我完全不认识你
I have no idea who you are.
你现在最好还是出去吧
You'd be taking your leave now.
谢谢
Thank you.
啊 你在收拾行李
Yes,you are packing.
漂洋过海到殖民地去
Sailing for the colonies.
我都知道
I know all about it.
计划有变
Change of plans.
这是怎么回事
What's this then.
我们在开派对吗
Are we having a party.
对 告别派对
Yes,a farewell party.
一只海鸥落到了他头上然后开始扑腾翅膀
A seagull landed on his head and started flapping.
能出来放松一个晚上
I can't tell you how great it feels.
真是兴奋到无以言表
To have a funny night out,right,guys.
然后另外一只海鸥过来了
And this other seagull comes.
释放所有的压力
Take out all the pressure,you know.
总之 从那以后 再也没人想吃披萨了
Anyway,so no one had any pizza after that.
首先 能被他老人家亲自选中
Of course,I can't really complain being.
我没什么可抱怨的
Hand-picked by the big man himself.
我其实不应该提这件事
No I'm not really supposed to talk about it.
因为那可是Metatron
Cause it's Metatron.
Metatron怎么了
What about Metatron.
他很依赖我
He's come to depend on me.
你们知道的 我们很铁
So,you know,we're tight.
我不得不承认
And I have to say.
我开始赞赏这个疯子的远见了
I've come to appreciate the mad man's vision.
他还有远见
His vision.
他把我们全部赶出了天堂
He pulled us all out of heaven.
不 不 不 目光放远点
No,no,no,big picture.
他在重整天堂
He's giving the place a makeover.
带回被选中的少数天使
Bringing back the chosen fews.
从少数被选中的开始
Starting with the chosen,chosen fews.
如果你们懂我的意思
If you know what I mean.
现在可是敏感时期
These are dangerous times.
你最好管好自己的嘴巴
You have to be careful what you say.
搞不好隔墙有耳
You never know who might be listening.
我什么也没说
I said nothing.
呵 你说的够多了
Ho...you said plenty.
很显然你觉得有必要讨论一下
Apparently you felt the need to discuss.
自己和Metatron的关系
Your relationship with Metatron.
你们的战略
Your strategies.
不
No.
机密信息
Privileged information.
像你这样口无遮拦 会有报应的
You speak that freely and there are consequences.
你待会儿就知道了
As you are about to find out.
难道是 他
Is that..him.
没错
It is.
就是这儿吗
This is the address.
对
Yeah.
跟我来 司令要见你们
If you follow me,commander will see you now.
还司令呢
The commander.
长官
Sir.
嗯 解散
Umm,dismissed.
他有时候是挺古板的
He can be a little stuffy.
成司令了啊
So commander.
不是我的主意
Not my idea.
群龙无首 他们坚持要我带头
They had no leader and they insist on following me.
对 我们懂的
Yeah,no,we get it.
你是个摇滚明星
You are a rock star.
Bartholomew死了
Bartholomew was dead.
Malachi也被Gadreel杀了
Malachi was murdered by Gadreel.
Metatron现在如日中天
And with Metatron as powerful as he is now.
我必须采取行动
I needed to do something.
天使之战在所难免 是吗
So this war between angels is really gonna happen,ha.
如果能通过外交手段摆脱Metatron
Not if I can find a diplomatic option for.
何乐而不为
Getting rid of Metatron.
祝你好运啊
Good luck with that.
Dean 天使们互相残杀
Dean,this angel on angel violence.
这事儿该有了结了
It has to end.
必须有人站出来
Someone has to say enough.
那个人就是你喽
And that someone is you.
我请你们来 就是为了这个
It brings me to...why you are here.
我们收押了一个俘虏
We have a prisoner.
是Metatron内线里的一个
It's an angel from Metatron's inner circle.
我需要套出他们的阴谋
I need to know what they are planning.
目前为止他只字未吐
So far he's revealed nothing.
意思是你唱完白脸
So you are done with the rough stuff.
让我们唱红脸
And you want us to be your goons.
因为你们干这种事情比较在行
Well you've had success at these situations before.
如果你不愿意 我能理解
If you don't want to do it,I understand.
谁说我不愿意
Who says I don't want to do it
(克利夫兰市 俄亥俄州)
事情是这样的 同学们
So here is the thing,boys and girls.
我们有个大麻烦
We have a crisis.
坦诚地讲 是我惹来的麻烦
Admittedly,the crisis of my own making.
在我不在的日子里
In my extended absense.
忙着处理国家的敏感事务
Where I handle sensitive matters of the state.
Abaddon混进了我们的队伍
Abaddon made enrolled to my following.
制造混乱
Creating chaos.
所以我指望你们 我的亲信
So I look to you,my trusted advisors.
能让我们重拾信心
To restore confidence.
抚慰民心
To soothe those jangled nerves.
放话下去 你们的王回来了
Spread the word,the king is back.
帝国即将再度崛起
And the kingdom is once again on sound footing.
愿意和我一起的
So,all those with me.
说 有
Say yo.
有
Yo.
我指现在我是和你在一起
I mean I'm literally with you.
而不是要追随你
Not with-you with-you.
你们这些叛徒
You betrayed me.
你们将见识到刑讯史上最残忍的酷刑
No one in history of torture's been tortured.
比你们所经历过最残忍的酷刑还要残忍
With torture like the torture you will be tortured with.
同学们放轻松
Relax everyone.
你们的效忠我笑纳了
You did the new queen and I saw it.
将来你们会前途无量的
You are sitting at the popular kids' table.
Crowley 坦率的讲
Crowley,let's talk turkey.
我知道是你帮Winchesters兄弟
I know you helped the Winchesters get their hands.
拿到了初刃 对吗
On the first blade,yes.
我还听说他们中有一个背负着该隐之印
And I'm hearing one of them also has the mark of Cain.
真是太糟糕了 因为初刃是唯一一件
All bad news since the Blade is the one thing.
能把我
That can bring about my.
带进坟墓的武器
Utter destruction.
无意冒犯
To be indelicate.
但是你可听好了 小乖乖
But here's the thing,pet.
你也别想逃
Same goes for you.
一旦我死了
And once I'm gone.
你以为那两帅帅的兄弟会追杀谁
Who do you think is next on those cute boys' list.
这就是了
That's right.
现实点吧
So let's get real.
跟我合作 解决了Winchester兄弟
Join me and taking out the Winchesters.
还有那把破刀
And the ridiculous blade.
然后我们两个再慢慢玩
And then,we'll deal with each other.
我把话说清楚
To be clear.
我不会跟你合作的 决不
I'll not be joining you,ever.
除了 你死的时候
Except,at your death scene.
场面一定很壮观
Where shall burst into sun.
再见 你没有可以威胁到我的筹码
Goodbye,you have no hold out of me.
哦是吗
Oh no.
Gavin 亲爱的
Gavin,honey.
跟爹爹问好
Say hello to daddy.
你怎么
How did you.
我知道一两个咒语 Crowley
I know a spell or two,Crowley.
你疯了吗
Are you mad.
这就是你的筹码
This is your big card.
这个孩子和我互相看不对眼
The boy and I loathe each other.
我已经说得很明白了
I made it clear in the past.
我才不关心这臭小子会出什么事
I don't care what happens to the little bugger.
是吗
Oh.
但那是很久之前了 不是吗
But that was before,wasn't it.
我很了解你那点小麻烦
See I know all about your little problem.
嗜血成瘾
Binging on blood.
接近变为人类的边缘
Going right at the edge of being human.
那么多人类的感情
All of those human feelings.
我戒了
I'm clean.
我还是愿意赌上一赌
And I'm willing to bet that.
在某个角落还是留下了一丝人性
There's a smidgin of humanity in there somewhere.
不可能
Not a chance.
我的眼睛
My eyes.
天呐
Oh my goodness.
你知道这些小伎俩吓唬不了我的
You know these coolish party tricks don't impress.
我见过更可怕的 做过更糟的
Seen worse,done worse.
不
No.
你这招儿对我不管用 红发妹
You're playing a weak hand,Red.
求你了 不要
I beg you,please.
你赢了
You've made your point.
快住手
Now stop.
好吧
Sure.
你们在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
我没什么可说的
I have nothing to say.
这可不见得
We disagree.
折磨我没用的
There's no use to torture me.
我是受过训练的士兵 没用的
I am a trained commando,it won't work.
是吗 你这是在邀请我
Wow,well you just ask me to dance.
Dean Dean
Dean!Dean.
他要是死了我们就什么都不知道了
He won't be telling us anything,dead.
另外 我觉得
Besides,you know I'm really starting to realise that.
他可能真的什么都不知道
He probably doesn't know anything.
只是假装自己是重要的一员
He's probably just pretending at the bar.
他很可能什么都不是
Most likely he's a nobody.
我的意思是 你想想看
I mean,you do the math.
这个Ezra 会是Metatron的精英手下吗
Ezra here,is one of the Metatron's elite posse.
别逗了
Really.
Metatron最信任的人之一
One of Metatron's most trusted is.
就在酒吧胡混 随随便便谈论自己的上司
Hanging out the bars,blabbing about the boss.
根本说不通啊
That's not making sense.
除非Metatron就喜欢给自己招蠢货
Only if Metatron's purposely surrounding himself with losers.
就是啊 对吧
Exactly,right.
这家伙究竟为啥在这儿
What's this guy even doing here.
估计只是在幻想而已
Guess a wanna-be.
如果他真是核心人物的话 他怎么不在天堂
I mean if he was a key player,he would be up in heaven.
和Metatron一起演大戏
With Metatron where all the actions.
没错
Exactly.
我也有可能是个诱饵
What if I'm a decoy.
或是卧底
Or in deep cover.
好心酸
It's pathetic.
估计他掉线之后 就没跟天堂联络过
Probably hasn't even been to heaven since his fall.
肯定没
Of course not.
我当然有
Yes,I have.
哥们 大门都被封印了 谁都进不去
Buddy,the gates are sealed,no one can get in.
谁跟你说大门了
Who said anything about gates.
有秘密入口还要门干吗
You don't need gates when you have a private portal.
好吧
All right.
就算地球上有个传送门
If there was a doorway onto earth.
- 天使也会知道的 - 是啊
- The angels would've sensed it - Yeah.
- 天使们不可能不知道的 - 说的是
- You can't have something like that - No.
如果那个传送门到处移动 就真的没人知道了
You can if it moves around from place to place.
上司想放哪儿就放哪儿
If it's wherever the boss wants it to be.
你不是我爸爸
You are not my father.
我爸爸是Fergus McLeod
My father was Fergus McLeod.
他是一个小裁缝 酒鬼 怪物
A simple tailor,a drunk,a monster.
那就是他没跑了
Sounds about right.
他一点都不像你
He looked nothing like you.
我亲手埋葬了他
And I buried him.
291年里会发生很多事
A lot can change 291 years.
什么
What.
这玩意儿能烤熟鸽子吗
Can you cook a pigeon on it.
他还是没反应过来 对吧
Not terribly quick,is he.
我的天啊
Holly mother of god.
我们在星星里
We're amongst stars.
这儿是天堂吗
Are we in heaven.
你们一定是天使了
You must be angels.
我明白了
I see.I got it.
所以你听说
So you heard a rumor.
Metatron手里有个秘密传送门
About Metatron's secret portal.
于是你就决定誓死追随他了是吗
And you decided to run with it.
不是听说
It's not a rumor.
我亲眼看见了
He showed me.
我明白了
I get it.
他是个脑残粉
He's a fan.
一个脑残粉
A fan.
你是个脑残粉
You are a fan.
就因为你对Metatron一见钟情
Just because you're hot for Metatron.
不管是贾斯汀比伯还是贝克汉姆之类的
Or Bieber,or Beckham.
就算你对他们无所不知
Just cause you know everything about them.
也不代表你就了解他们
Doesn't mean you actually know them.
他们可能完全不知道有你这么个人
Or that they may not know you exist.
- 这么说太打击人了 - 我是说可能
- Oh,that's cold,Sam. - I'm just saying,man.
我可是被Metatron亲自接见
I was interviewed personally by Metatron.
竞争一个重要职位
For a key post.
所以呢
Yeah.
那你跟我说说
Maybe you can tell me.
是什么让你失去了这个重要职位
Why you were out of your key post.
然后沦落到这个地方来
And you're hanging down here instead.
你戳他软肋了
Um...now,that blows.
他落选了
He got passed over.
我是最后几个候选者之一
I was a finalist.
我的天 你差一点就成功了
Oh,man.He's so close.
结果还是被刷下来了
And then get kicked down stairs.
我为你深表同情
It sucks to be you.
能被选入的人都是凤毛麟角
Hardly anybody was chosen.
此外陆军部队也是一个重要的力量
And ground-force is still a very important assignment.
能成为行动小组的候选人都是一种荣耀
It's an honor to have even been considered for the squad.
什么行动小组 根本没什么行动小组
What squad?There was no squad.
你当然不知道 这是最高机密
Yeah,says you.It's a highly guarded secret.
所以你究竟要做什么呢
And what would you be doing exactly.
等一下
Wait a second.
劳驾
Just please.
我来理清一下思路
Clarify this for me.
你非常想要这份工作
You desperately wanted this job.
但是你根本连要干什么都不知道
But you didn't know what it was.
除非你被选中
Well,until you are chosen.
你不会被告知任何有关工作的事情
The exact nature of the mission was kept a secret.
并且几乎没有人被选中
And hardly anyone was chosen.
一脸蠢相 怪不得被抓起来了
Dimbod,no wonder he got bumped.
是啊
Yeah.
陆军部队 秘密行动小组
Grand forces,elite secret squad.
Metatron到底要干什么
What's Metatron gearing up for.
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么我们不直接
Why don't we shove somebody.
去那个天堂后门看看呢
Through the back door of heaven and find out.
哦对 那个破玩意儿是便携的 找不到
Oh,wait.No.It's portable and can't be found.
你卖了你的灵魂
You sold your soul.
就这样卖了
Sold it.
就为了下半身的幸福
For an extra three inches of willy.
情况不一样了
Priority has changed.
我以前可没有现在这么人见人爱
I wasn't the bon vivant that I am now.
简单来说
I will simplify.
我的灵魂在地狱里恶魔化了
My soul did a stint in hell where it became demonized.
所以我必须附到别人身上
Then I had to possess on another person.
这样才能跟人类正常来往
So I can traffic with the living.
还有什么不明白吗
Any of this sticking.
我怎么可能跟一个恶魔厮混在一起
I can't be consorting with a demon.
不 不是什么普通的恶魔
No.Not just any demon.
我是王 地狱之王
I am the King.The King of Hell.
现在你又开始担心
And there you were.
你老爹也许不会有多大作为了
Worrying the old man wouldn't amount to much.
真是难以置信
It's unbelievable.
我们离开时 他还是好好的
I mean he was fine when we left him.
我几乎没怎么碰过那个人
I've barely touched the guy.
他还被锁着 没有武器
Still shackled,no weapon.
不会是自杀
Wouldn't be suicide.
不 有天使杀了他
No.This was an angel kill.
好吧 我想说的是
Okay well I'm gonna say it.
也许你的行动泄露了
Maybe you operation has been hacked.
你身边有Metatron的内鬼
Metatron's got somebody in the inside.
我确定这里所有人都是忠诚的
I was sure everyone here was loyal.
所有人都是因为同一个目标聚在一起
Finally united by a common cause.
这正是问题所在
That's a problem.
你不相信有人会欺骗你
You don't think anybody's lying.
我觉得所有人都在说谎
I think everybody is lying.
这是天赋
It's a gift.
我们去周围转转
Let's do some nosing around.
Sam 等等
Sam,do you have a moment.
什么事
Yeah,what.
我想问你Gadreel的事情
I want to ask you about Gadreel.
他附在你身上的时候
The time he possessed you.
我不是特想谈论这件事儿
It's not really something I'd like to.
Sam 拜托了
Sam,please.
他并没有完全附身
He didn't possess me,completely.
更像是我们在共同使用一个身体
More like we share the housing.
我还是我
I was still me.
你有感觉到他的存在吗
Did you ever sense a presence.
我不知道我感觉到了什么
I don't really know what I felt.
也许我也发现自己不是一个人
Maybe that I wasn't completely alone.
你曾经觉得自己受到威胁了吗
Did you ever feel threatened.
不 我觉得他总是惶惶不安
No.More that he wasn't at rest.
更像是他有没完成的事情
Like he has unfinished business.
现在我们对他有了进一步的了解
Now that we know more about him.
我觉得他认为自己被误解了
I'd say he felt misunderstood.
但他并不危险对吗
But,but not a danger.
并不怀有敌意
Not hostile.
并不
No.
但很明显 我错了
I was wrong,obviously.
他杀了Kevin
He killed Kevin.
我为什么会恨你
Why do I hate you.
我打你
Well,I beat you.
饿你饿到半死
Starved you.
经常喝醉
Came home drunk.
继续打你
Beat you some more.
醒来就是宿醉的感觉 然后接着打你
Woke up hungover,and yeah,well,beat you.
其实这很正常啊 我也没有模板来对比
In all fairness,I didn't really have any role models.
我妈是巫师
My mother was a witch.
我从小到大 一直都觉得我自己一无是处
I grew up thinking,knowing I was nothing.
卑贱到可以忽略不计
Less than nothing.
你恨不得把我当马来使唤
You worked me harder the a horse.
从来不让我去学校
Never let me go to school.
到今天 我连字都不认得
Till this day,I can't read.
哪有那么严重
It's overrated.
大部分欧洲人都不识字
Most of Europe couldn't read.
想认字吗
You wanna read.
现在看
Read.
海盗打败了圣徒
Some buccaneers beat the saints.
有可能吗
Can this be.
我能识字了
I can read.
地狱之王 大权在握
King of Hell,plenty of perks.
这么说 如果你是王
So,if you're a king.
那我不就是
That would make me.
王子
Prince.
你还说我什么都没给过你
You say I've...never given you anything.
这不是个头衔吗
A title.
如果我承认你是我老爸
And if I was to accept you as my father.
你能让我脱离地狱的苦海吗
You could keep me from eternally burning in hell.
不管我犯了什么原罪
No matter my sins.
你在跟我谈判吗
You're negotiating with me.
真不愧是我儿子
That's my boy.
说不定真能成
This might work out.
活这么大以来 我第一次
For the first time in my entire life.
感觉到生活有了目标
I can see possibilities.
看到未来
A future.
等你把我送回去
Just as soon as you take me back to my own time.
我就能登上去新世界的游轮
And I can aboard that ship to the new world.
说到那个游轮
About that ship.
怎么了
What about the ship.
这不重要
It's not important.
告诉Abaddon我准备好跟她谈了
Can tell Abaddon I'm ready for that chat.
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
谢谢你一个人来
Thank you for coming alone.
我在Sam Winchester身体里的时候见过你
I've seen you through Sam Winchester's eyes.
他信任你
And he trusts you.
你有维持荣誉的名声
You have a reputation for honor.
是有人这么认为
In some circles.
说到名声
As for reputations.
你同样名声在外
Yours proceeds you.
在伊甸园里发生的事不是传说的那样
What happened in the Garden was not my doing.
我知道你觉得自己被误解了
I know you feel misunderstood.
你急于救赎你自己
And you're eager to redeem yourself and.
可能还有别的
Maybe more.
你是在暗示我支持Matatron
You refer to my support of.
重新建立天堂这件事吗
Metatron's campaign to rebuild the heaven.
你说是支持吗 你为他招募天使
Your support?You've recruited for him.
你为他大开杀戒
You've killed for him.
我知道 你相信大局为重
I know you truly believe it's for the greater good.
但是你跟错了人
But you've placed your faith in the wrong master.
- 你不了解他 - Gadreel 我太了解他了
- You don't know him - I know him too well,Gadreel.
我犯过同样的错误 导致了天使的坠落
I made the same mistake which let to the fall.
也给我带来了第二次机会
Which led to my second chance.
- 这一切不只是为了你自己 - Castiel
- This is about more than just you - Castiel.
你是让我背弃忠诚吗
Are you suggesting I change loyalties.
我是让你重新站回
I'm suggesting you reclaim your original loyalty.
天堂这边 重拾我们最初的使命
To the heaven and the mission we were meant to serve.
这不就是我正在做的吗
I thought that was exactly what I was doing.
你被蒙蔽了
You've been deceived.
不管你承受了多少痛苦
And as bad as you've had it.
不管你被关了多久
Although centuries locked away.
要是让Metatron来统治 只会更糟
It will be much worse under Metatron.
Castiel
Castiel.
手给我
Give me your hand.
这就对了
That's it.
放下刀 Dean
Drop the Blade,Dean.
Dean
Dean.
发什么呆呢 接电话啊
What's wrong with you,you hear your phone.
真是时候
It's about time.
你跑什么鬼地方去了
Where the hell have you been.
我说过了 一有Abaddon的消息就告诉你
I told you I'd be in touch when I found Abaddon.
我现在不是在打电话吗
Well,I'm in touch.
- 你在哪儿 - 首先
- Where are you - First thing's first.
我会给你初刃所在地的位置
I'll give you the location of the First Blade.
你们去拿初刃
You two fetch it.
我看住Abaddon
I'll keep her in my sights.
然后我们一起除掉她
Then we'll remove her from the payroll.
永远
For good.
噢 天啊 Crowley
Oh,come on,Crowley.
真的非要把初刃藏在尸体里吗
Really have to hide the blade in the corpse.
不是放在尸体旁边 是在尸体里
Not with a corpse...but in a corpse.
我得承认
I gonna say.
打死我也不会想到在尸体里
It's not the first place I'd look.
好吧 开工
Alright,here we go.
Dean 你听到了吗
Dean?Did you hear that.
我想是地狱猎犬
I am guessing hellhound.
快跑
Go go.
你好呀
Hello.
该死的Crowley坟墓有看守者
Damn is Crowley,grave is guarded.
怎么可能
It's absurd.
地狱猎犬
A hellhound.
不不不 那是她的本职工作
No no no no she was collected.
当然了
The hell she was.
伙计们
Guys.
没人敢违背地狱之王
Time was no one would dare disobey the king.
赶紧的
Guys.
我要开免提了
I'm gonna put you on speaker.
Juliet 我是爸爸
Juliet,it's papa.
退下
Stand down.
不用谢了
You are welcome.
好吧
Alright.
我继续了
Going in.
嘿 知道吗
Hey you know what.
或许应该我来做
Maybe I should do this.
Sammy 没事的 我能很安全的取出来而不用
Sammy,it's fine,I...I can safely grab it without.
你知道
You know.
好吧 让我们去杀了那个地狱骑士
Well,let's go kill a Knight of Hell.
你在说什么
What are you talking about.
我回去之后当然会登上那艘船
Of course I'll board in a ship when I go back.
我想过我自己的生活
I want to go back to my lives.
不是什么好想法
Not a good idea.
我要去殖民地
I am going to the Colonies.
我正在一点点接近目标
I am working my way across.
我说到做到
I am giving you my word.
Gavin 听爸爸的
Gavin,listen to your father.
我都是
I know what's.
为了你好
Best for you.
儿子
Kids.
松鼠
Squirrel.
真希望你对你老爹态度好点儿
Have you're nice to your father.
什么 闭嘴 我们已经拿到初刃了
What,shut up,we've got the blade.
拿到了啊
You do.
马上带着初刃过来
We need to get it here at once.
克利夫兰市 洪堡酒店 顶层公寓
Cleveland,Humboldt hotel,penthouse,of course.
你到了以后 我会带你去找Abaddon
When you get here,I'll take it to Abaddon.
我会把她引出来
I'll draw her out.
然后你们给她致命一击
And then you can skewer the ignorant hag.
正送过来呢
Just sending in.
我们已经在路上了
We are on our way.
Dean
Dean.
你要一直走
You need to get a move on.
今天可是离开Poughkeepsie的好日子
It's a good day to drive from the Poughkeepsie.
什么意思 我们离那儿十万八千里呢
What are you talking about,we're not even near there.
像我说的 你需要马上离开Poughkeepsie
Like I said,you need to leave the Poughkeepsie right away.
一切正常吧
So are we good.
是的
Yeah.
很好
Nice.
不过现在的情况是
But here's the thing.
你跟男孩们磨蹭的
You have been plodding with those boys.
太久了
For some time now.
他们到这里时
When they get here.
你
It will be you.
Winchester兄弟
The Winchesters.
初刃和我
The first blade and a little old me.
一个都不能少
In one place.
虽然我不介意跟老对头合作
Now I don't mind stiff odds.
但是 你我都是明白人
But let's be reasonable.
你疯了吗
You lost your mind.
从Henry Winchester那
A little tricky.
学来的小把戏
From Herry Winchester.
他对我也这么干过
He pulled the same stunt on me.
子弹上刻了恶魔陷阱
I have devil's trap carved on the bullets.
你不会伤的很重
You are not seriously damaged.
只是瘫痪了而已
Just paralysed.
真不关我的事
I had nothing to do with this.
如果我知道
I never would have agreed to meet.
有人会去暗杀你
If I thought concealed assassins.
我是不会同意和你见面的
Would going to try to attack you.
我希望你相信我
I hope you know this.
为什么要告诉我
Why are you telling me this.
即使你和我
Even though you and I.
是站在对立的阵线上
Are on the opposite side of this situation.
我也相信我们都是为了荣誉
I believe there must be honor.
纵使这意味着战争
Even it matters a war.
但是这发生的一切
But what happened.
不是恰恰证明了我对Metatron的看法吗
Doesn't it prove my point about Metatron.
你来见我本是好意
You met with me in good faith.
但是他欺骗了你
But he lied.
利用你来抓我
And he used you to get to me.
Castiel
Castiel.
正如当年你孱弱的判断力
Just as poor judgment.
让你被囚禁多年一样
Undid you all those centuries ago.
你错信了Metatron
You mistaken trust Metatron.
这会让你付出代价的
It will bring you down again.
我对他做了承诺
I gave him my word.
你难道想让我现在对他宣战吗
Do you expect me to come make war on him.
不 完全不是
No,not at all.
我只希望你
I want you.
就保持你现在的状态
To stay right where you are.
告诉我Metatron在密谋什么
Just give me reports on what Metatron is planning.
以及他何时出手
And when he will strike.
我们刚刚还说到荣誉
And the honor we were speaking of.
显而易见
Obviously.
我的队伍里有Metatron的人
Metatron has someone inside my camp.
所以他才知道我们要见面
That's how he knew we were meeting.
我只是以其人之道还治其人之身
Just fighting fire with fire.
你考虑一下
Consider my offer.
好吧 走吧
All right,let's do this.
等等 等一下
Wait,wait,wait,hold on a second.
我们上去之前
We should give this place once over.
再讨论一下
Before we go up there.
好吧 为什么
Okay,why.
Crowley说这栋楼
Crowley said he saw.
地下室里有不少恶魔
Some demons hiding down the basement.
他说他自己会去料理
He will check them out himself.
但是 如果我们从下面走 他就暴露了
But we're going back at Abaddon that he'd be seen.
他什么时候说这些了
When did he say all this.
电话上说的
On the phone.
他也有可能是说
Look,it might mean.
Abaddon知道他在这儿了
She knows that he's here,okay.
你去地下室检查一下
Why don't you check out the basement.
我去看看主楼
I will take a look at the main floor.
你好啊 Dean
Hello,Dean.
真喜欢你眼睛里疯狂的嗜血冲动
Love the crazy blood lust in your eyes.
我们别浪费时间了
Let's not waste time.
我带你去找Abaddon
I will take you to Abaddon.
离得不远
It's not far.
手拿初刃的男孩
A boy and his blade.
依旧无法与女王抗衡
And still,no match for the new queen.
好了 首先
So,first.
你会痛苦地死掉
You will die,painfully.
然后Crowley会亲眼看着他儿子死去
And then Crowley will watch the son die.
死法同上
Ditto.
然后就轮到他自己
And the king himself.
初刃也会被毁掉
And blade destroyed.
这任务清单可不短
That's quite a to-do-list.
Dean
Dean.
Dean 住手
Dean,stop.
可以住手了
You can stop.
你们至少帮我解决一下这个
You could at least,help me with this.
我们饶了你一命 Crowley
We didn't kill you,Crowley.
即使杀你易如反掌
Even though it would've been very easy.
这还不够吗
Isn't that enough.
那是你们欠我的
You owe me.
而且没有人想谢谢我警告你们这是个陷阱吗
While I get no credit for warning you this was a trap.
Poughkeepsie 想起来了没
Poughkeepsie,ring a bell.
又要矫情了
I sense drama.
我还是无法接受Crowley居然有个儿子
I just still can't get over with the fact that Crowley has a son.
顺便问问 他怎么样
How's he doing by the way.
你觉得呢
What do you think.
你应该明白吧 他必须回到过去
You get this,he's gotta go back,right.
回到他本来的时间点
To his own time.
如果他回去了 他就注定会登上那艘
The lad goes back,his destiny is to board a ship.
去美国的船
Bound for America.
那艘船在风暴里沉没了
That ship went down in a storm.
无一人生还
All hands were lost.
他现在有一个机会 可以改变自己的命运
He has one chance in this world to change his life.
难道还要继续上演悲剧吗
You want that all ended in tragedy.
没什么好说的了
Well,I don't know what to tell you.
规矩就是规矩 他必须回去
That's the rule,he goes back.
所有的传说都指明了一件事
The lore all says the same thing.
只要对历史作出一点更改
You change any one thing in the past.
所有与之有关联的事都会被影响
It'll rip all the fact and impact everything in the follows.
行行好
Please.
论不按规矩出牌 有人比得过你们两个吗
No one bends the rules than you two bend the rules.
一个小破孩掀不起多大的风浪
He's one misfit kid,he impacts no one.
你不能破坏规矩 明白吗 你不能
You don't bend the rule,okay?You don't.
我们会把他带回基地
We'll take him back to the bunker.
想办法破掉那个咒语
And figure out the spell.
事情只能这样解决
That's the way it's gonna be.
至少让我去说声再见
At least say goodbye.
当我彻底摆脱了人性的折磨 我会欢欣雀跃的
I'll cheer the day when the last trace of humanity leaves me.
情之一字啊
Feelings.
该死的 Crowley
Damn it,Crowley.
那艘船沉了
The ship went down.
我的余生真是多姿多彩啊
Well,that's a good fit with the rest of my life.
用不着哭鼻子 Gavin
Mustn't snivel,Gavin.
过去你的命运也许是如此 可是现在不会了
It might fit the old lives,this one could be different.
我对21世纪一无所知
I don't know the first thing about the 21st century.
你会没事儿的
You'll be fine.
小心便宜威士忌和便宜妓女就行
Just avoid cheap whisky and cheap hookers.
看看我
Look at me.
都慈父了
Getting all fatherly.
所以你是在说再见了
So this is goodbye then.
是的
Yes.
永远
Forever.
除非你小子把自己弄死了
Unless of course I catch you smoked.
我会亲自去揍你一顿的
In which case,I'll smack you stupid.
再见了
Goodbye then.
还有 谢谢你
And thank you.
父亲
Father.
可以了 可以了
Easy,easy.
拥抱什么的就不用了
As you were.
再见 Gavin
Goodbye,Gavin.
别到处提你是地狱王子的事儿
Don't go mentioning that all Prince of Hell thing.
很多小圈子不是很喜欢这个名字
Doesn't play too well in most circles.
我没把Crowley的警告告诉你
I didn't tell you about the warning.
因为我知道 如果我跟你说了实话
Because I knew exactly what you'll do.
你肯定会确保
You'll make sure that.
跟着我一起走进那件屋子
You're right along aside me going into that room.
你是说像我们经常干的那样吗
You mean like what we always do.
因为我们是合作关系
Because we're actually partners in this.
因为我们彼此照顾
And we watch each other's backs.
我不指望你能理解
I don't expect you to understand.
说说看
Try me.
我第一次把初刃拿在手上
First time I touched that blade.
我就知道
I knew.
我知道我停不下来了
I knew I wouldn't be stopped.
我知道我会不顾一切杀死Abaddon
I knew I would take down Abaddon and.
挡我者杀之
Anything else if I had to.
不是因为逞英雄那档子事儿 不是的
And it wasn't a hero thing you know it wasn't.
我握着它的时候内心很平静
It was just calm.
我知道
I knew.
而且我必须独自承担这个 Sammy
And I had to go it alone Sammy.
当然
Of course.
你又觉得我需要你的保护了
So it's just another time when you had to protect me.
你可能会被Abaddon抓住要挟我
You could have gotten nabbed by Abaddon.
她就有机会溜走了
She could have bargained her way out.
我们这次可输不起
We couldn't afford to screw this up.
听着
Look.
我很高兴你成功了
I'm glad it worked out,okay.
我也很高兴那刀能给你力量
I'm glad the blade gives you strength.
或者让你冷静下来 或者别的什么
Or calm or whatever.
但是Dean 我想说
But Dean I gotta to say.
我觉得这把刀可能有别的影响
I'm started to think the blade is doing something else too.
是吗 比如什么
Yeah like what.
我不确定 比如对你有影响
I don't know like something to you.
听着
Look.
我在想
I'm thinking.
在我们确定能够解决掉Crowley之前
Until we know for sure that we're gonna kill off Crowley.
我们不如把刀放远一点
Why don't we store the blade somewhere distant.
锁在一个安全的地方
Locked it up somewhere safe.
好吗
OK.
不行
No